Previously on Prison Break...
Losing a brother, the massive
hole that leaves in your life.
Like the same massive hole
losing a husband makes.
- Your brother's dead, Lincoln.
- How do you explain that?
- Lincoln Burrows.
- Jacob.
- Uncle Lincoln!
- Hey!
911. I have an armed
intruder in my house.
We've awoken something...
Something people are trying
to hide about Michael.
- I don't know who we're fighting.
- Let's go to Yemen and find out.
You don't know a damn thing about Yemen.
I'll find someone who does.
The country's falling apart.
Everyone wants out.
Welcome to the civil war.
Come quickly, or we'll all be dead!
- Who's that contact again?
- A woman named Sheba.
Michael's caught in the
middle of something big.
Kaniel Outis is
- a big-time terrorist.
- We've arranged
a visit to Ogygia Prison.
That mean Michael's in there?
Michael?
My name isn't Michael, and
I don't know who you are.
_
Michael, what are you doing, damn it?!
The fighting in Yemen intensified today
as ISIL forces get ever
nearer to the capitol.
The rebels, who have the
stated intent of taking over
the country and establishing
a radical caliphate,
are also bent on freeing their leader,
Abu Ramal, who was captured by
the government five years ago.
Ramal is known for his
extreme views and practices,
from using young girls as sex slaves,
to a medieval brand of justice
that includes public beheadings
and executions in the street.
Ramal is currently being held in Yemen's
most notorious
penitentiary, Ogygia Prison.
_
Psst.
This is it.
Whip, get up here.
Is it happening?